<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GooseMod</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on GooseMod</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GooseMod v12.1</title><link>/blog/gm-v12.1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v12.1/</guid><description>GooseMod v12.1 is now out! Various improvements with Store UI, storage, settings, and more. Store Ludicrous speed. The Store should now be quite faster, especially on low-end hardware. Carousel controls in banner images. Also made modal opening more obvious via cursor. Search text hints. Now shows no results text for no results, and hints to go to an other category if there are results in that and not the current category.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v12.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v12.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v12.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v12.0 is now out! Better translations, store improvements, and more. Translations GooseMod now supports almost entire translations. Almost all of GooseMod now supports translations, instead of previously where it was only some features and only a few languages. Current languages with translations: German, Chinese (Simplified), Chinese (Traditional), Dutch, Finnish, French, Hungarian, Polish, Portuguese (Brazil), Russian, Thai, Ukrainian. Store Decreased data usage and improved performance of Store pages.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v11.1</title><link>/blog/gm-v11.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v11.1/</guid><description>GooseMod v11.1 is now out! Features plenty of fixes, tweaks, and general polish. Store Repos modal now has a new header. Now reports statistics of repos (theme, plugin, and developer count) and matches Discord&amp;rsquo;s new styling. Removed toast appearing on module updates. Settings Removed GM Storage Impl from settings sidebar. Also added it to &amp;ldquo;Copy Debug Info&amp;rdquo; setting output. Tweaks and Fixes Fixed Tour crashing. Fixed some plugins failing to save settings.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v11.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v11.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v11.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v11.0 is now out! Features internal rewrite, error fail-safing, plus a whole bunch of other improvements and tweaks. Internal Rewrite GooseMod is now almost half the size as it was before. Smaller size should help load times and reduces impact of new additions in the future! Better for GooseMod&amp;rsquo;s future. GooseMod now uses Rollup; this helps developing GooseMod for the future: improving efficiency and speed of development. Error Fail-safing GooseMod is now resistant to crashes.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v10.2</title><link>/blog/gm-v10.2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v10.2/</guid><description>GooseMod v10.2 has been released! Features PGP verification for repos, plus some settings and API improvements. PGP Verification Repos now have PGP verification support. Repos can now be signed by their maintainers and verified within GooseMod. This should both improve security generally and for some specific attacks. The main advantage PGP adds is that it verifies repos are made and released by their owners. This prevents someone else taking over and publishing malicious updates as the repo would have to be signed with the same private key, which they should not have access to.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v10.1</title><link>/blog/gm-v10.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v10.1/</guid><description>GooseMod v10.1 has been released! Features internal rewrites, new profile store, and lots of tweaks and fixes. Internal Rewrites Rewrote logger output to use text and nicer colors. Now easier to look at and filter. Rewrote React utils library. Now supports new React used in Discord Canary and now a bit more efficient. Rewrote Webpack library. Additionally also now a bit more efficient and generally better. Profile Store Developer&amp;rsquo;s GooseMod modules are now listed under a category in their user profile.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v10.0.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v10.0.0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v10.0.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v10.0.0 has been released! Features a new storage system and rewritten injection for desktop resulting in faster and lighter injection. Storage New storage system. GooseMod now uses WebExtension storage for storing GooseMod preferences, installed modules, cache, etc. This should make storing more reliable, secure, and generally better. Desktop Using Extension GooseMod for desktop clients now uses the GooseMod for Web extension internally. This simplifies code (avoiding reuse / complications) and should result in faster (~50%) and lighter injection.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.6.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.6.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.6.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.6.0 has been released! Features various improvements and tweaks like Store images modal, new settings, a new API, and other tweaks and fixes. Store Images are now shown larger when clicked. When clicking a header image, a modal now appears showing all the images for the module (with larger sizing). Filter times are now faster. It should be about twice as fast due to some fixes and optimisations under the hood.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.5.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.5.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.5.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.5.0 has been released! Includes a new first time tour, store improvements, and some minor fixes. New First Time Tour New tour system. There is now a tour when opening GooseMod for the first time (since this update). It covers the core features of GooseMod: the Store, settings and community (focusing on the Discord server). Store Improvements Added separate imported tab in Home header. Now has a tab just for imported modules, and a main Store tab for all.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.4.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.4.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.4.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.4.0 has been released! A minor update compiling together many various tweaks and fixes. Fixes and Tweaks Dramatically decreased Store loading times (40s -&amp;gt; 3s) when loading GooseMod sometimes. Mostly when opening GooseMod for the first time, purging cache, or sometimes randomly. Renamed Module Store to Store fully throughout. Added refresh prompt when purging cache via setting. Fixed some small UI bugs with Firefox. Fixed GooseMod commands not working.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.3.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.3.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.3.0 has been released! More of a minor update, featuring various improvements to repos and the Store. Repos Improvements More reliable modal. Repos which fail to load now show up so you can remove / disable them. Simplified internals. Mostly a pro for us, repos are now easier to work with and simpler internally in GooseMod. Store Improvements Loading is more reliable. Most bugs for being stuck in loading have been fixed, apologies for any issues.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.2.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.2.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.2.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.2.0 has been released! Includes a new backup system and more Store and settings improvements. Backup System New backup system. There is a new backup system in GooseMod settings allowing you to backup your modules and settings. Backing up produces a backup file which you can then use to restore later on. Store Improvements Ludicrous speed. Clicking on home items is now significantly faster than before. Squashed bugs.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.1.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.1.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.1.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.1.0 has been released! A followup to v9, bringing various quality of life improvements and fixes. Settings Improvements Home now has improved loading. Should be faster and no longer showing it&amp;rsquo;s loading for the rest of time. Settings which need a refresh now have a neat prompt. Instead of the disclaimer text, it now has a prompt for you after you change them. Icons now have tooltips. To clear up any confusion, hovering over any setting icons (experimental or debug) now shows a tooltip saying what they mean.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v9.0.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v9.0.0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v9.0.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v9.0.0 has been released! React settings at long last! React Settings It&amp;rsquo;s finally here: React settings. Long requested by some, it&amp;rsquo;s finally done. We rewrote essentially over 2.5 thousand lines of JS so now our settings are made using React (instead of DOM which it used to use). What this means for you: More fitting UI. GooseMod&amp;rsquo;s settings are now even more fitting with Discord&amp;rsquo;s, now featuring animations, new colors, and finer looking items, making it now more seamless than ever.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v8.12.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v8.12.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v8.12.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v8.12.0 has been released! More of a minor release with various fixes and quality of life tweaks. Home Show loading indicator whilst loading fully. Used to just wait for any modules, not all. Fixed Store pages not opening when clicked if user has no DMs. Store Fixed id cache not being invalidated every day. Added localised path support for repo images. Like using /images/file.png. Settings Use Discord&amp;rsquo;s new green color in switches.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v8.11.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v8.11.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v8.11.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v8.11.0 has been released! Highlights: New translucent toast design. Various fixes. Toasts New translucent design. Patcher API Fixed UserBadges sizes being off. Fixes Fixed GooseMod changelog not removing footer and changing title when appearing at startup. Fixed store in settings expanding too wide.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v8.10.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v8.10.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v8.10.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v8.10.0 has been released! Highlights: A new Store design with categories. Various Store and home placement improvements. Store New categories design. Having headings and horizontal sections of cards for categories like top starred and recently updated. Added repos button to header via cloud icon instead of being in settings. Added shadow to cards. Removed Discord&amp;rsquo;s default toolbar from the toolbar. Reduced delay between id cache queue API requests.</description></item><item><title>GooseMod v8.9.0</title><link>/blog/gm-v8.9.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/gm-v8.9.0/</guid><description>GooseMod v8.9.0 has been released! Highlights: Improvements to the new home placement. Minor store UI improvements. Home Made GooseMod section collapsible via an icon in the header. Added updated badge to modules which have been updated within 5 days. Added update button to page headers for easy updating of store repos. Made new modules appearing in home pages easier. Specifically without needing to click off then back to home.</description></item><item><title>New GooseMod Site</title><link>/blog/new-gm-site/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/new-gm-site/</guid><description>Welcome to the new GooseMod site! It has been remade from scratch with the aim of being both minimal and elegant, whilst also providing a good level of information (new screenshots and stats). Hope you all enjoy, and as always you can give us feedback in our Discord.</description></item></channel></rss>